The Tomorrow War 2 is a action, science fiction film directed by Chris McKay.
The sequel to The Tomorrow War (2021).
The Tomorrow War is a 2021 American military science-fiction action film directed
by Chris McKay, written by Zach Dean, and starring Chris Pratt.
It was produced by David Ellison, Dana Goldberg, Don Granger, David S.
Goyer, Jules Daly, and Adam Kolbrenner, with a
supporting cast featuring Yvonne Strahovski, J.
Simmons, Betty Gilpin, Sam Richardson, Edwin Hodge, Jasmine
Mathews, Ryan Kiera Armstrong, and Keith Powers.
It follows a mix of present-day soldiers and civilians sent into the
future to fight and stop a devastating alien swarm.
Originally set for theatrical release by Paramount Pictures, the film's distribution rights were acquired by
Amazon Studios due to the COVID-19 pandemic, and digitally released on July 2, 2021, via Prime Video.
With a budget of US$200 million, the film was one of the most
expensive films to debut on a streaming platform.
The Tomorrow War received mixed reviews from critics, with praise for the concept, action sequences, and
performances (particularly Pratt and Richardson), but criticism for its derivative execution.
A sequel is in development.
The tone is thought_provoking.